Bohdan Khvorostovskyi

ABOUT ME

I've been developing my skillset over the past 2 years and I have knowledge of JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, MongoDB, Redux, and React Native. I believe I am ready to contribute to a team and am looking for opportunities. I am also interested in connecting with like-minded people to improve my skills and share interests. You will not find a harder working and more focused person.

EXPERIENCE

Hungry Ghost, New York, USA— Operations supervisor, Barista

May 2019 - Present

Brooklyness, New York, USA— System Mechanic

May 2019 - July 2019.

Vitasko, New York, USA— General Laborer

May 2018 - May 2019.

Autoliv, Jelcz-Laskowice, Poland — System Operator

May 2017 - Dec 2017.

Thomas Dieng Farm, Memmingen, Germany — Agricultural Engineer

Oct 2015 - Apr 2016.

Django, Moscow, Russia — Bartender

Oct 2014 - Feb 2015.

New York, NY, USA

(347)-529-9448

bohdankhv@gmail.com

https://khvorostovskyi.com

https://github.com/BohdanKhv

LANGUAGES

English, Russian, Ukrainian.

SKILLS

React.JS, MongoDB, Node.JS, Express.js, Redux, React Native, HTML, CSS, JS, GitHub, Git

EDUCATION

Podilskyi Agrarian Technical University, Ukraine

Master's in Agriculture Engineering

Oct 2011 - Feb 2018

PROJECTS

More projects can be found on my GitHub.

Serverless stock market portfolio builder http://stokin.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/

Typing game

http://typing-g.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/

Math game

http://math-g.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/

Drawing app

http://react-drawing-app.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/

Artificial life

http://artificial-life.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/

Personal project https://thall.us

Spotify API project https://thallify.com

Linktree clone

https://link-tree-clone.herokuapp.com/

Business schedule app

https://mern-schedule-app.herokuapp.com/

Social media app

https://faskme.herokuapp.com/

Chat app

https://woh-chat-app.herokuapp.com/